I wasn't able to take my video this
morning so I'm making it now at 9:30 at
night after a full day out with my
daughter so I am exhausted
I don't have two full days well but I
had when we first got went to the peony
which is fair in Vancouver and one of
the things they had was a futuristic
house
tell us futuristic ghosts and old
touring it I had this I mean a lot of
the ideas that are in there I've had
already and they're not even real ideas
like meeting sorry they're not real
technology it's their conception of what
could be in the future and when Telus
owns it I mean it's not super scary tell
this isn't a horrible company but it's
still it's weird for them to be like and
we'll be in contact with your doctor's
office and your grocery store and and
but if we own that and plus it's super
elitist that like okay so you get to
have body scans and you get to have
fresh food groaning your house and know
all the nutrients for it and prepare
food easily but of course I mean it's
gonna be expensive but in the system I'm
proposing we put all design it together
and I'll own it together and figure out
how like if something made sense that
you all get it yeah there's a lot of
probably wasn't so exhausted but
it's a system where you do have a smart
house that orders your groceries keeps
track of it you can say what you want to
eat it or order it deliver it to you you
can coordinate anything with your
neighbors you can and it walks you
through how to do the recipe and tracks
your health in real time as well as
coordinating with your neighbors and
tracking everyone's health right like if
there's an increase in cancer in your
neighbourhood they might be a reason why
and yeah all those things are kind of
scary at the corporation's then and not
scary if we own it together and we
get together and use it for the greater
good and vote on using it for the
greater good so it's a short video I'm
exhausted and I just it's one of the I
think this is day 10 like she's been
bigger but we're one-tenth done the
videos of me trying to figure out how to
explain although I did today also have I
had to come my I mean I was with my
child and she got back around when she's
normally asleep I and when she's overly
tired takes her forever to go to bed so
I had to take her for a walk even though
I was exhausted and while I was out for
a walk I had actually had a way of kind
of explaining what I was gonna do I
don't want to come in and a half I
didn't I'm a bored supporter on my phone
so I'll listen to it tomorrow and see if
it makes sense when I'm not as exhausted
as I am now okay well thank you for
joining me watching this subscribe and
like if you would like to see more
thanks